[
    {
        "question": "Which of the following is not a character on \"'Friends'?",
        "correctAnswer": "Jackson",
        "answer1": "Ross",
        "answer2": "Monica",
        "answer3": "Phoebe",
        "answer4": "Rachel"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the Old English meaning of the word \"Earth?\"",
        "correctAnswer": "Ground",
        "answer1": "Dirt",
        "answer2": "Center",
        "answer3": "Ground",
        "answer4": "Grass"
    },
    {
        "question": "What are the three primary colors?",
        "correctAnswer": "Red, blue, yellow",
        "answer1": "Red, blue, green",
        "answer2": "Red, blue, yellow",
        "answer3": "Yellow, black, blue",
        "answer4": "Red, blue, white"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the currency of Sweden?",
        "correctAnswer": "Swedish krona",
        "answer1": "Euro",
        "answer2": "Swedish krona",
        "answer3": "Swedish pound",
        "answer4": "Swedish forint"
    },
    {
        "question": "How many pockets are there on a snooker table?",
        "correctAnswer": "6",
        "answer1": "2",
        "answer2": "4",
        "answer3": "6",
        "answer4": "8"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the tallest mountain in the world?",
        "correctAnswer": "Mount Everest",
        "answer1": "K2",
        "answer2": "Mount Everest",
        "answer3": "Manaslu",
        "answer4": "Makalu"
    },
    {
        "question": "What are the only two consecutive prime numbers?",
        "correctAnswer": "2 & 3",
        "answer1": "2 & 3",
        "answer2": "1 & 2",
        "answer3": "0 & 1",
        "answer4": "3 & 4"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the name of Robin Williams film where he dressed up as an elderly nanny?",
        "correctAnswer": "Mrs. Doubtfire",
        "answer1": "Jumanji",
        "answer2": "Mrs. Doubtfire",
        "answer3": "Good Will Hunting",
        "answer4": "Patch Adams"
    },
    {
        "question": "How many points is a touchdown worth?",
        "correctAnswer": "6",
        "answer1": "4",
        "answer2": "3",
        "answer3": "5",
        "answer4": "6"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which Disney movie is the villain Clayton from?",
        "correctAnswer": "Tarzan",
        "answer1": "Tarzan ",
        "answer2": "Beauty and the beast",
        "answer3": "Sleeping beauty",
        "answer4": "The little mermaid"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which U.S. states is known for peaches?",
        "correctAnswer": "Georgia",
        "answer1": "Florida",
        "answer2": "Maryland",
        "answer3": "Georgia",
        "answer4": "Arkansas"
    },
    {
        "question": "Fe is the symbol of which chemical symbol?",
        "correctAnswer": "Iron",
        "answer1": "Silver",
        "answer2": "Iron",
        "answer3": "Gold",
        "answer4": "Titanium"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the date of ''The Devils Night''?",
        "correctAnswer": "30-Oct",
        "answer1": "30-Oct",
        "answer2": "31-Oct",
        "answer3": "01-Nov",
        "answer4": "29-Oct"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which New York City neighborhood was ''Gossip Girl'' filmed in?",
        "correctAnswer": "Upper East Side",
        "answer1": "Upper West Side",
        "answer2": "Soho",
        "answer3": "Upper West Side",
        "answer4": "Washington Heights"
    },
    {
        "question": "When did World War I begin?",
        "correctAnswer": "1914",
        "answer1": "1918",
        "answer2": "1909",
        "answer3": "1921",
        "answer4": "1914"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Han Solo's ship called in Star Wars?",
        "correctAnswer": "Millennium Falcon",
        "answer1": "Executor",
        "answer2": "Imperial Star Destroyer",
        "answer3": "Millennium Falcon",
        "answer4": "Home One"
    },
    {
        "question": "What's the name of the toy cowboy in the movie \"Toy Story?\"",
        "correctAnswer": "Woody",
        "answer1": "Buzz",
        "answer2": "Rodney",
        "answer3": "Willie",
        "answer4": "Woody"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the name of Simba's father in the Lion King?",
        "correctAnswer": "Mufasa",
        "answer1": "Scar",
        "answer2": "Pumba",
        "answer3": "Mufasa",
        "answer4": "Hamlet"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the first-ever Disney film?",
        "correctAnswer": "Snow White and the Seven Dwarfs",
        "answer1": "Cinderella",
        "answer2": "Pinocchio",
        "answer3": "Mary Poppins",
        "answer4": "Snow White and the Seven Dwarfs"
    },
    {
        "question": "What direction can kangaroos not walk?",
        "correctAnswer": "Backwards",
        "answer1": "Backwards",
        "answer2": "Diagonally",
        "answer3": "Sideways",
        "answer4": "Forward"
    },
    {
        "question": "What color blood does an octopus have?",
        "correctAnswer": "Blue",
        "answer1": "Red",
        "answer2": "Blue",
        "answer3": "Black",
        "answer4": "Clear"
    },
    {
        "question": "What percent of Antarctica is ice-free?",
        "correctAnswer": "Less than 1%",
        "answer1": "0.05",
        "answer2": "Less than 1%",
        "answer3": "0.02",
        "answer4": "0.1"
    },
    {
        "question": "What type of dog does the royal family famously own?",
        "correctAnswer": "Corgi dogs",
        "answer1": "Pugs",
        "answer2": "English terriers",
        "answer3": "Corgi dogs",
        "answer4": "Dachshunds"
    },
    {
        "question": "How many pairs of wings do bees have?",
        "correctAnswer": "2",
        "answer1": "1",
        "answer2": "2",
        "answer3": "3",
        "answer4": "4"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is a doe?",
        "correctAnswer": "A female deer",
        "answer1": "A male deer",
        "answer2": "A female deer",
        "answer3": "A male moose",
        "answer4": "A female moose"
    },
    {
        "question": "On the farm, what is a kid?",
        "correctAnswer": "A baby goat",
        "answer1": "A baby pig",
        "answer2": "A baby cow",
        "answer3": "A baby horse",
        "answer4": "A baby goat"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who is the patron saint of Ireland?",
        "correctAnswer": "St Patrick",
        "answer1": "St James",
        "answer2": "St George",
        "answer3": "St Patrick",
        "answer4": "St Nicolas"
    },
    {
        "question": "If you suffer from arachnophobia, which animal are you scared of?",
        "correctAnswer": "Spiders",
        "answer1": "Dogs",
        "answer2": "Bugs",
        "answer3": "Bats",
        "answer4": "Spiders"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which place is called \"the happiest place in the world?\"",
        "correctAnswer": "Disneyland",
        "answer1": "Hollywood",
        "answer2": "Las Vegas",
        "answer3": "Disneyland",
        "answer4": "New York"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the smallest state in America?",
        "correctAnswer": "Rhode Island",
        "answer1": "Rhode Island",
        "answer2": "Delaware",
        "answer3": "Connecticut",
        "answer4": "Hawaii"
    },
    {
        "question": "What kind of tree do acorns come from?",
        "correctAnswer": "Oak",
        "answer1": "Pine",
        "answer2": "Oak",
        "answer3": "Birch",
        "answer4": "Maple"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who is not one of the seven dwarves in Snow White?",
        "correctAnswer": "Lovely",
        "answer1": "Lovely",
        "answer2": "Grumpy",
        "answer3": "Sneezy",
        "answer4": "Sleepy"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which movie is Prince Charming from?",
        "correctAnswer": "Cinderella",
        "answer1": "Snow White",
        "answer2": "Cinderella",
        "answer3": "Sleeping beauty",
        "answer4": "Little mermaid"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the name of Mickey Mouse's pet dog?",
        "correctAnswer": "Pluto",
        "answer1": "Pluto",
        "answer2": "Donald",
        "answer3": "Minnie",
        "answer4": "Scoopy"
    },
    {
        "question": "What kind of tree do prunes come from?",
        "correctAnswer": "Plum tree",
        "answer1": "Apple tree",
        "answer2": "Plum tree",
        "answer3": "Pear tree",
        "answer4": "Lemon tree"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which state was the 50th state to join the union?",
        "correctAnswer": "Hawaii",
        "answer1": "Hawaii",
        "answer2": "Alaska",
        "answer3": "California",
        "answer4": "Washington"
    },
    {
        "question": "The Kangaroo Hoppet is a long distance cross-country skiing race that is held in which county?",
        "correctAnswer": "Australia",
        "answer1": "New Zealand",
        "answer2": "Australia",
        "answer3": "Canada",
        "answer4": "China"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which river flows through London?",
        "correctAnswer": "The Themes",
        "answer1": "The Loire",
        "answer2": "The Seine",
        "answer3": "The Themes",
        "answer4": "The Main"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which is the largest city in Wales?",
        "correctAnswer": "Cardiff",
        "answer1": "Cardiff",
        "answer2": "Swansea",
        "answer3": "Newport",
        "answer4": "York"
    },
    {
        "question": "What does the F stand for in FBI?",
        "correctAnswer": "Federal",
        "answer1": "Foreign",
        "answer2": "Federal",
        "answer3": "Fraud",
        "answer4": "Flight"
    },
    {
        "question": "So far, which continent has hosted the Olympics the most times?",
        "correctAnswer": "Europe",
        "answer1": "Asia",
        "answer2": "Europe",
        "answer3": "South America",
        "answer4": "North America"
    },
    {
        "question": "What sea is next to Saudi Arabia?",
        "correctAnswer": "Red sea",
        "answer1": "Black sea",
        "answer2": "Arabian sea",
        "answer3": "Red sea",
        "answer4": "Persian gulf"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the little dot above a lowercase “i” or “j” called?",
        "correctAnswer": "Tittle",
        "answer1": "Tittle ",
        "answer2": "Point",
        "answer3": "Blop",
        "answer4": "Finck"
    },
    {
        "question": "In 1917, Finland declared its independence from which country?",
        "correctAnswer": "Russia",
        "answer1": "Sweden",
        "answer2": "Denmark",
        "answer3": "Russia",
        "answer4": "Germany"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the name of a word that is spelled the same forwards and backward?",
        "correctAnswer": "Palindrome",
        "answer1": "Enneagram",
        "answer2": "Palindrome",
        "answer3": "Anagram",
        "answer4": "Anonym"
    },
    {
        "question": "The aardvark is native to which continent?",
        "correctAnswer": "Africa",
        "answer1": "South America",
        "answer2": "North America",
        "answer3": "Asia",
        "answer4": "Africa"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who created Iron Man?",
        "correctAnswer": "Stan Lee",
        "answer1": "Jack Kirby",
        "answer2": "Stan Lee",
        "answer3": "John Byrne",
        "answer4": "Jim Lee"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the singular of timpani?",
        "correctAnswer": "Timpano",
        "answer1": "Timpano",
        "answer2": "Timpan",
        "answer3": "Timpaine",
        "answer4": "Timper"
    },
    {
        "question": "What South American animal is the world's largest rodent?",
        "correctAnswer": "The capybara",
        "answer1": "Nutria",
        "answer2": "Cape porcupine",
        "answer3": "The capybara",
        "answer4": "Paca"
    },
    {
        "question": "In the U.S., freedom of speech is guaranteed by which Constitutional Amendment?",
        "correctAnswer": "1st",
        "answer1": "1st",
        "answer2": "2nd",
        "answer3": "3rd",
        "answer4": "4th"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who was the fugitive in the 1993 movie by the same name?",
        "correctAnswer": "Dr. Richard Kimble",
        "answer1": "Cosmo Renfro",
        "answer2": "Samuel Gerard",
        "answer3": "Dr. Richard Kimble",
        "answer4": "Dr. Charles Nichols"
    },
    {
        "question": "What video game character was originally given the name Jumpman?",
        "correctAnswer": "Mario",
        "answer1": "Luigi",
        "answer2": "Mario",
        "answer3": "Link",
        "answer4": "Donkey Kong"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who wrote the young adult novel \"Holes\"?",
        "correctAnswer": "Louis Sachar",
        "answer1": "Markus Zusack",
        "answer2": "Lauren Oliver",
        "answer3": "Louis Sachar",
        "answer4": "Maureen Johnson"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who directed the 1974 film \"Chinatown\" starring Jack Nicholson?",
        "correctAnswer": "Roman Polanski",
        "answer1": "Woody Allen",
        "answer2": "Steven Spielberg",
        "answer3": "Rob Reiner",
        "answer4": "Roman Polanski"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the NATO phonetic alphabet word for \"Q\"?",
        "correctAnswer": "Quebec",
        "answer1": "Queen",
        "answer2": "Qatar",
        "answer3": "Quebec",
        "answer4": "Mozambique"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which US state's official flower is the Saguato Cactus?",
        "correctAnswer": "Arizona",
        "answer1": "Nevada",
        "answer2": "New Mexico",
        "answer3": "Texas",
        "answer4": "Arizona"
    },
    {
        "question": "The Hugo Award is an award given in what field?",
        "correctAnswer": "Science fiction",
        "answer1": "History",
        "answer2": "Science fiction",
        "answer3": "Physics",
        "answer4": "Mathematics"
    },
    {
        "question": "What author created the character of Miss Marple?",
        "correctAnswer": "Agatha Christie",
        "answer1": "Arthur Conan Doyle",
        "answer2": "Anna Katharine Green",
        "answer3": "Agatha Christie",
        "answer4": "Graham Greene"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who sang the hit song \"Confide in Me\" in 1994?",
        "correctAnswer": "Kylie Minogue",
        "answer1": "Madonna",
        "answer2": "Tina Turner",
        "answer3": "Olivia Newton-John",
        "answer4": "Kylie Minogue"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which famous entrepreneur is credited with inventing the weekend?",
        "correctAnswer": "Henry Ford",
        "answer1": "Thomas Edison",
        "answer2": "Willis Carrier",
        "answer3": "Henry Ford",
        "answer4": "Ken Olsen"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who had a hit with the song and album \"Sweet Dreams (Are Made Of This)\"?",
        "correctAnswer": "Eurythmics",
        "answer1": "Dido ",
        "answer2": "Kate Bush",
        "answer3": "Sinead O'Connor",
        "answer4": "Eurythmics"
    },
    {
        "question": "Originally, Jack-O'-lanterns were made from which type of vegetable?",
        "correctAnswer": "Turnip",
        "answer1": "Potato",
        "answer2": "Rutabaga",
        "answer3": "Turnip",
        "answer4": "Beet"
    },
    {
        "question": "What fast food chain uses the slogan \"We Have The Meats\"?",
        "correctAnswer": "Arby's",
        "answer1": "Five guys",
        "answer2": "Arby's",
        "answer3": "Wendy's",
        "answer4": "In-n-out"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which king decided to transform Versailles into a royal court in 1661?",
        "correctAnswer": "Louis XIV",
        "answer1": "Louis XVI",
        "answer2": "Louis X",
        "answer3": "Louis XIV",
        "answer4": "Louis IX"
    },
    {
        "question": "\"Old Bill\" is a nickname or slang for whom?",
        "correctAnswer": "Police offices",
        "answer1": "Police officers",
        "answer2": "Cowboys",
        "answer3": "Alcoholics",
        "answer4": "Firemen"
    },
    {
        "question": "Rennet, an enzyme-filled juice from animal stomachs, is used in the making of what?",
        "correctAnswer": "Cheese",
        "answer1": "Yogurt",
        "answer2": "Haggis",
        "answer3": "Cheese",
        "answer4": "Gummy bears"
    },
    {
        "question": "In modern badminton, how many points typically win a singles game?",
        "correctAnswer": "21",
        "answer1": "21",
        "answer2": "17",
        "answer3": "35",
        "answer4": "26"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which TV series from the 1980s featured a character named Uncle Jesse?",
        "correctAnswer": "Full House",
        "answer1": "Full House",
        "answer2": "Proud Family",
        "answer3": "Cheers",
        "answer4": "Growing Pains"
    },
    {
        "question": "What body of water is between Scotland and Denmark?",
        "correctAnswer": "The North Sea",
        "answer1": "The Danish Sea",
        "answer2": "The Balic Sea",
        "answer3": "The North Sea",
        "answer4": "The Scottish Sea"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who provided the original voice for Shrek?",
        "correctAnswer": "Mike Myers",
        "answer1": "Mike Myers",
        "answer2": "Chris Miller",
        "answer3": "Eddie Murphy",
        "answer4": "John Lithgow"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who keeps telling Captain Kirk that Earthlings are \"highly illogical\"?",
        "correctAnswer": "Spock",
        "answer1": "Scotty",
        "answer2": "Spock",
        "answer3": "Leonard McCoy",
        "answer4": "Christopher Pike"
    },
    {
        "question": "What were the first two Western countries that the Nazis invaded during World War II?",
        "correctAnswer": "Norway and Denmark",
        "answer1": "Netherlands and Belgium",
        "answer2": "Belgium and France",
        "answer3": "Norway and Denmark",
        "answer4": "Denmark and Netherlands"
    },
    {
        "question": "In what non-Spanish-speaking city would you find the Spanish Steps?",
        "correctAnswer": "Rome",
        "answer1": "Lisbon",
        "answer2": "Milano",
        "answer3": "Cannes",
        "answer4": "Rome"
    },
    {
        "question": "What New York City avenue divides the east side from the west side?",
        "correctAnswer": "Fifth",
        "answer1": "Sixth",
        "answer2": "Seventh",
        "answer3": "Fifth",
        "answer4": "Fourth"
    },
    {
        "question": "How many squares are there on the traditional \"Snakes & Ladders\" board?",
        "correctAnswer": "100",
        "answer1": "80",
        "answer2": "60",
        "answer3": "100",
        "answer4": "120"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the official language of Papua New Guinea?",
        "correctAnswer": "English",
        "answer1": "English",
        "answer2": "Spanish",
        "answer3": "French",
        "answer4": "Portuguese"
    },
    {
        "question": "What classic novel's subtitle is \"There and Back Again\"?",
        "correctAnswer": "The Hobbit",
        "answer1": "Treasure Island",
        "answer2": "2000 Leagues Under The Sea",
        "answer3": "Tom Sawyer",
        "answer4": "The Hobbit"
    },
    {
        "question": "In what month did Hurricane Katrina hit New Orleans?",
        "correctAnswer": "August",
        "answer1": "August",
        "answer2": "March",
        "answer3": "June",
        "answer4": "October"
    },
    {
        "question": "What iPod was the first without a screen or a scroll wheel?",
        "correctAnswer": "Ipod shuffle",
        "answer1": "Ipod mini",
        "answer2": "Ipod 1",
        "answer3": "Ipod shuffle",
        "answer4": "Ipod original"
    },
    {
        "question": "In what city would you find the infamous Alcatraz?",
        "correctAnswer": "San Francisco",
        "answer1": "San Diego",
        "answer2": "San Francisco",
        "answer3": "New York City",
        "answer4": "Chicago"
    },
    {
        "question": "In Germany, where would you be if you were in a \"Krankenhaus\"?",
        "correctAnswer": "Hospital",
        "answer1": "Bakery",
        "answer2": "Police station",
        "answer3": "Hotel",
        "answer4": "Hospital"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the most mountainous country in Europe?",
        "correctAnswer": "Switzerland",
        "answer1": "Switzerland",
        "answer2": "Austria",
        "answer3": "France",
        "answer4": "Italy"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is eaten traditionally in the UK the day before Ash Wednesday?",
        "correctAnswer": "Pancakes",
        "answer1": "Beans",
        "answer2": "Pancakes",
        "answer3": "Waffles",
        "answer4": "Pudding"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which mixed drink was made famous by rapper Snoop Doggy Dogg in the 1990's?",
        "correctAnswer": "Gin and Juice",
        "answer1": "Weed juice",
        "answer2": "Gin and juice",
        "answer3": "Jack and coke",
        "answer4": "Ginger beer"
    },
    {
        "question": "Kandor is the former capital city of what fictional planet?",
        "correctAnswer": "Krypton",
        "answer1": "Arrakis",
        "answer2": "Krypton",
        "answer3": "Coruscant",
        "answer4": "Tatooine"
    },
    {
        "question": "Ford produced the Model T in only what color after 1913?",
        "correctAnswer": "Black",
        "answer1": "Black",
        "answer2": "Grey",
        "answer3": "Blue",
        "answer4": "White"
    },
    {
        "question": "What did Wednesday Addams call her headless doll on \"The Addams Family\"?",
        "correctAnswer": "Marie Antoinette",
        "answer1": "Joan of Arc",
        "answer2": "Marie Antoinette",
        "answer3": "Mother Mary",
        "answer4": "Anne Frank"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who played the leading female part in the 1954 film \"A Star Is Born\"?",
        "correctAnswer": "Judy Garland",
        "answer1": "Barbra Streisand ",
        "answer2": "Kathleen Crowley",
        "answer3": "Judy Garland",
        "answer4": "Janet Gaynor"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the more common name for grape sugar?",
        "correctAnswer": "Glucose",
        "answer1": "Glucose",
        "answer2": "Sugar cane",
        "answer3": "Fructose",
        "answer4": "Sucrose"
    },
    {
        "question": "How many of the Seven Summits are over 20,000 feet high?",
        "correctAnswer": "3",
        "answer1": "0",
        "answer2": "1",
        "answer3": "2",
        "answer4": "3"
    },
    {
        "question": "Tiffany and Co. has a registered trademark on its signature shade of what color?",
        "correctAnswer": "Blue",
        "answer1": "Green",
        "answer2": "Silver",
        "answer3": "Gold",
        "answer4": "Blue"
    },
    {
        "question": "In 2006, David Bowie was awarded a Grammy award for what?",
        "correctAnswer": "Lifetime Achievement",
        "answer1": "Artist of the Century",
        "answer2": "Lifetime Achievement",
        "answer3": "Worldwide Icon",
        "answer4": "Songwriter of the Century"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the capital of Kuwait?",
        "correctAnswer": "Kuwait City",
        "answer1": "Kuwait City",
        "answer2": "Doha",
        "answer3": "Manama",
        "answer4": "Muscat"
    },
    {
        "question": "Where are the Whitsunday Islands located?",
        "correctAnswer": "Australia",
        "answer1": "Philippines",
        "answer2": "Australia",
        "answer3": "Indonesia",
        "answer4": "New Zealand"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who opened the first \"cinema\" in Paris in 1895?",
        "correctAnswer": "The Lumiere Brothers",
        "answer1": "The Skladanowsky Brothers",
        "answer2": "The Lumiere Brothers",
        "answer3": "Georges Méliès",
        "answer4": "Robert W. Paul"
    },
    {
        "question": "What trademarked name for in­line skates was also its first successful brand name?",
        "correctAnswer": "Rollerblades",
        "answer1": "Rollerblades",
        "answer2": "Rollerskates",
        "answer3": "Rollies",
        "answer4": "Rollers"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was Marilyn Monroe’s natural hair color?",
        "correctAnswer": "Red",
        "answer1": "Blonde",
        "answer2": "Brown",
        "answer3": "Black",
        "answer4": "Red"
    },
    {
        "question": "How many weeks before Christmas does the 2003 film \"Love Actually\" begin?",
        "correctAnswer": "Five",
        "answer1": "Two",
        "answer2": "Three",
        "answer3": "Seven",
        "answer4": "Five"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was Lyndon B. Johnson's middle name?",
        "correctAnswer": "Baines",
        "answer1": "Baines",
        "answer2": "Brandon",
        "answer3": "Barron",
        "answer4": "Barry"
    },
    {
        "question": "How many of the seven dwarfs had mustaches?",
        "correctAnswer": "None",
        "answer1": "None",
        "answer2": "One",
        "answer3": "Two",
        "answer4": "Three"
    },
    {
        "question": "Hippopotomonstrosesquipedaliophobia is the fear of what?",
        "correctAnswer": "Long words",
        "answer1": "Air bubbles",
        "answer2": "Hippos",
        "answer3": "Long words",
        "answer4": "Magic spells"
    },
    {
        "question": "In \"Spirited Away\", Yubabas giant baby Boh gets turned into what?",
        "correctAnswer": "Mouse",
        "answer1": "Sheep",
        "answer2": "Mouse",
        "answer3": "Rock",
        "answer4": "Swan"
    },
    {
        "question": "What used to be called the apple of love or love apple ?",
        "correctAnswer": "Tomato",
        "answer1": "Orange",
        "answer2": "Pomegranate",
        "answer3": "Tomato",
        "answer4": "Child"
    },
    {
        "question": "Golda Meir was the leader of what country?",
        "correctAnswer": "Israel",
        "answer1": "Israel",
        "answer2": "Armenia",
        "answer3": "Turkey",
        "answer4": "Georgia"
    },
    {
        "question": "In which game might you \"peg out\"?",
        "correctAnswer": "Cribbage",
        "answer1": "Poker",
        "answer2": "Cribbage",
        "answer3": "Mahjong",
        "answer4": "FreeCell"
    },
    {
        "question": "In what 1863 short story does Philip Nolan renounce his US citizenship?",
        "correctAnswer": "The Man Without a Country",
        "answer1": "All the Colors of Goodbye",
        "answer2": "Names\/Nombres",
        "answer3": "The Man Without a Country",
        "answer4": "Dead Men’s Path"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who was the first woman to serve on the U.S. Supreme Court?",
        "correctAnswer": "Sandra Day O'Connor",
        "answer1": "Ruth Bader Ginsburg",
        "answer2": "Sandra Day O'Connor",
        "answer3": "Sonya Sotomayor",
        "answer4": "Elena Kagan"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is a group of crows called?",
        "correctAnswer": "A murder",
        "answer1": "A frock",
        "answer2": "A gang",
        "answer3": "A murder",
        "answer4": "A squad"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which artist is known as the \"Father of Impressionism\"?",
        "correctAnswer": "Camille Pissarro",
        "answer1": "Clade Monet",
        "answer2": "Camille Pissarro",
        "answer3": "Pierre-Auguste Renoir",
        "answer4": "Edgar Degas"
    },
    {
        "question": "What caused the Tacoma Narrows Bridge to collapse in 1940?",
        "correctAnswer": "Wind",
        "answer1": "Rain",
        "answer2": "Bombing",
        "answer3": "Weight",
        "answer4": "Wind"
    },
    {
        "question": "Where in the body are the adenoids?",
        "correctAnswer": "Nose",
        "answer1": "Throat",
        "answer2": "Ear",
        "answer3": "Nose",
        "answer4": "Liver"
    },
    {
        "question": "In which decade was Louise Brown, the first test tube baby born?",
        "correctAnswer": "1970s",
        "answer1": "1990s",
        "answer2": "2000s",
        "answer3": "1950s",
        "answer4": "1970s"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who wrote the novel Oryx and Crake?",
        "correctAnswer": "Margaret Atwood",
        "answer1": "Eve Babitz",
        "answer2": "Joan Diddion",
        "answer3": "Margaret Atwood",
        "answer4": "Sylvia Plath"
    },
    {
        "question": "What sea does Slovenia have water access to?",
        "correctAnswer": "Adriatic sea",
        "answer1": "Black sea",
        "answer2": "Adriatic sea",
        "answer3": "Baltic sea",
        "answer4": "Red sea"
    },
    {
        "question": "What US city is known as the \"City of Brotherly Love\"?",
        "correctAnswer": "Philadelphia",
        "answer1": "Phoenix",
        "answer2": "Portland",
        "answer3": "Miami",
        "answer4": "Philadelphia"
    },
    {
        "question": "What country borders Sierra Leone to the north?",
        "correctAnswer": "Guinea",
        "answer1": "Guinea",
        "answer2": "Ivory Coast",
        "answer3": "Mali",
        "answer4": "Chad"
    },
    {
        "question": "What inert gas gets trapped in the blood when a diver gets \"the bends\"?",
        "correctAnswer": "Nitrogen",
        "answer1": "Oxygen",
        "answer2": "Nitrogen",
        "answer3": "Lithium",
        "answer4": "Carbondioxide"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the name of the dictator of Haiti, who was also known as Papa Doc?",
        "correctAnswer": "Francois Duvalier",
        "answer1": "Antonio Thrasybule Kebreau",
        "answer2": "Franck Sylvain",
        "answer3": "Francois Duvalier",
        "answer4": "Henri Namphy"
    },
    {
        "question": "When Dwayne Wade briefly left the Miami Heat starting in 2016, which NBA team did he sign with?",
        "correctAnswer": "Chicago Bulls",
        "answer1": "Los Angeles Lakers",
        "answer2": "Chicago Bulls",
        "answer3": "Brooklyn Nets",
        "answer4": "Golden State Warriors"
    },
    {
        "question": "What comic strip did Scott Adams create while working for Pacific Bell?",
        "correctAnswer": "Dilbert",
        "answer1": "Dilbert",
        "answer2": "Garfield",
        "answer3": "Peanuts",
        "answer4": "The Far Side"
    },
    {
        "question": "What daytime soap opera takes place in the fictional town of Salem?",
        "correctAnswer": "Days of our Lives",
        "answer1": "General Hospital",
        "answer2": "Days of our Lives",
        "answer3": "Dallas",
        "answer4": "All My Children"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the name of the cloud-riding, glasses-wearing koopa in the Super Mario Bros. series?",
        "correctAnswer": "Lakitu",
        "answer1": "Lakitu",
        "answer2": "Kamek",
        "answer3": "Bootler",
        "answer4": "Dimentio"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who wrote the 1952 novel \"The Bridge over the River Kwai\"?",
        "correctAnswer": "Pierre Boulle",
        "answer1": "Arthur P. Jacobs",
        "answer2": "Pierre Boulle",
        "answer3": "Paul Dehn",
        "answer4": "Michael Wilson"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was Toula's wedding present from her parents in the movie \"My Big Fat Greek Wedding\"?",
        "correctAnswer": "A house",
        "answer1": "A car",
        "answer2": "A boat",
        "answer3": "Nothing",
        "answer4": "A house"
    },
    {
        "question": "What chapel do Cardinals congregate in to elect a new Pope?",
        "correctAnswer": "Sistine Chapel",
        "answer1": "Papal Chapel",
        "answer2": "Sistine Chapel",
        "answer3": "Niccoline Chapel",
        "answer4": "Redemptoris Mater Chapel"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which state is home to the oceanside city Myrtle Beach?",
        "correctAnswer": "South Carolina",
        "answer1": "Florida",
        "answer2": "California",
        "answer3": "Portland",
        "answer4": "South Carolina"
    },
    {
        "question": "How does Jack die in the movie \"The Shining\"?",
        "correctAnswer": "He freezes",
        "answer1": "He gets shot",
        "answer2": "He falls off a cliff",
        "answer3": "He freezes",
        "answer4": "He drowns"
    },
    {
        "question": "Entomologists study what?",
        "correctAnswer": "Insects",
        "answer1": "Bones",
        "answer2": "Maps",
        "answer3": "Nerves",
        "answer4": "Insects"
    },
    {
        "question": "Tercel is the name for the male of which animal?",
        "correctAnswer": "Hawk",
        "answer1": "Panda",
        "answer2": "Hawk",
        "answer3": "Camel",
        "answer4": "Cat"
    },
    {
        "question": "What constant is equivalent to 96,485 coulombs per mole of electrons?",
        "correctAnswer": "Faraday",
        "answer1": "Hartz",
        "answer2": "Maxwell",
        "answer3": "Faraday",
        "answer4": "Ampere"
    }
]
